

ANASTASIA TRIUKHAN

QA Engineer

Odesa, Ukraine

+380637348176

nastja.trjukhan@gmail.com

github

n <u>linkedin</u>

Being a Manual Quality Assurance Engineer for one year, I quickly got into the product and enhanced my abilities in VoIP and network, regression testing, teamwork, applied a lot of theoretical knowledge in practice, worked with the database, used existing tools and techniques to execute test cases. I also keep studying new things, learning the basics of Python and automation for future development.

SKILLS

Jira | Oracle SQL | mRemoteNG | GIT |
Postman | DevTools | Wireshark | WinSCP

EDUCATION

I.I.Mechnikov National University

International economic relations Odesa, 2012-2017

Hillel IT School

Manual Quality Assurance Engineer Odesa, June – November 2021

CERTIFICATIONS

Hillel IT School – https://certificate.ithillel.ua/view/72854512

WORK EXPERIENCE

AB-Soft, QA Engineer

Odesa, Januar 2021- May 2023

- Performing manual regression and functional testing using IP devices, Web, Desktop and mobile applications
- Bug tracking and Test Reporting, entering defects into bug-tracking system, verification and prioritizing bugs
- Updating manual test cases according to changes in technical documentation
- Collaborating with cross-functional teams
- · Performing certification and regression of new devices

PREVIOUS EXPERIENCE

Logistics economist, Odesa

2017-2021

SMM-manager, freelance

2012-2020